(
"ai_sub_version": "3.0.3",
"generated_at": "2026-07-07T02:11:28.759155",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 16,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
えー、みなちゃまー！
Uh, hello everyone!
本日は、轟はじめ生誕祭2026
Today, for Todoroki Hajime Birthday Celebration 2026...
「Rise in motion」に
...'Rise in motion'...
お越しくださいまして
...thank you so much for coming!
誠にありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
えー、開演に先立ちまして
Uh, prior to the start of the show,
みなちゃまにお願いとご案内をもちあげます！
we have some requests and guidance for everyone!
えー、当配信は一部収録を含みますが、
Uh, this stream contains some pre-recorded segments,
生配信部分もございますので、
but there are also live parts,
いっぱいコメントして盛り上げてください！
so please leave lots of comments and liven things up!
今もね、じわーっていっぱい、おお、こんちくわー、
Even now, there are so many comments like "Konchikuwa" (Hello),
きたー、パチパチパチと、ありがとうございます！
"It's here!" and clapping. Thank you so much!
えー、当配信のハッシュタグは
Uh, the hashtag for this stream is...
「#轟はじめ生誕祭2026」です！
..."#轟はじめ生誕祭2026"!
SNSでたくさんポストしていただけると嬉しいです！
I'd be glad if you could post a lot on social media!
えー、開演中はカメラやスマートフォンなどによる写真撮影大歓迎なので
Uh, taking photos with cameras or smartphones is highly welcome during the show,
たくさんポストして盛り上げていただけると幸いです！
so I'd appreciate it if you could post them and liven things up!
えー、それでは開演までしばらくお待ちください！
Uh, well then, please wait a little longer until the show starts!
えー、みなちゃまー！
Uh, hello everyone!
本日は、轟はじめ生誕祭2026
Today, for Todoroki Hajime Birthday Celebration 2026...
「Rise in motion」に
...'Rise in motion'...
お越しくださいまして
...thank you so much for coming!
誠にありがとうございます、パート２！
Thank you very much! Part 2!
どれどれ？なんか、ぐるぐるしてなさそうですね、みなちゃん！
Let's see. Looks like there's no buffering/lagging for everyone!
おおー、って、ワクワク、こんちくわ、と、大丈夫そうです！
Oh! "Excited," "Konchikuwa"... Looks like everything is fine!
開演に先立ちまして、みなちゃまにお願いとご案内を、ちょっともう一回もちあげます！
Prior to the start, let me make some requests and guidance for everyone once more!
えー、当配信は一部収録を含みますが、
Uh, this stream contains some pre-recorded segments,
生配信部分もございますので、いっぱいコメントして盛り上げていただけると嬉しいです！
but there are also live parts, so I'd be happy if you could leave lots of comments and liven things up!
きちゃん大丈夫とパート2、きちゃんありがとう！
Ki-chan, Daijoubu and Part 2, Ki-chan, thank you!
えー、今日の配信のハッシュタグは、ハッシュタグ「#おはししの生誕祭2026」です！
Um, the hashtag for today's stream is #OhashishiNoSeitansai2026!
SNSでたくさんポストしてください！
Please post a lot on SNS!
えー、開演中は、カメラやスマートフォンなどによる写真撮影、大歓迎です！
Also, during the show, taking photos with cameras or smartphones is highly welcome!
たくさんポストして、盛り上げていただけると嬉しいです！
I'd be happy if you post a lot to liven things up!
それでは、開演まで、今しばらくお待ちください！
Well then, please wait a little longer until the show starts!
BANZAI 無の有（なえ）の地に
BANZAI, in the land of nothingness/existence,
下らないお紛い物だってばラリアット
even worthless phonies get lariated!
[BANZAI / 作詞・作曲：マサ / 編曲：田中タロウ]
[BANZAI / Lyrics & Composition: Masa / Arrangement: Tanaka Taro]
喝采 消したる夜の門
Applause at the gates of the extinguished night,
鬱陶しい尾鰭を剥きながら僕は這う
stripping away annoying rumors as I crawl.
才能はとうにどうにかしちまってるけど
My talent has long been messed up,
歓声は脳にだっての
but the cheers are ringing in my brain.
愛にまみれた言葉で心拍数
My heart rate goes up with words covered in love,
生きてくたび胸は沈んでいく
each time I live, my chest sinks deeper.
どうなってんだろなプロローグ 揺れるの
What's going on with this prologue? It's wavering.
悔い積んでもしょうがねえ
There's no point in piling up regrets.
明日暮らせぐお金はどんだけ？
How much money do we have to live on tomorrow?
ああだこうだそんなもんか
Blah blah, is that all it is?
うるせえわな
Shut the hell up.
BANZAI 無の有の地に
BANZAI, in the land of nothingness/existence,
空回っていく脳を満たしてくれ
fill my spinning brain.
未来予想図なんか関係ない
A map of the future doesn't matter,
下らないお紛い物だってそれ
even if it's just a worthless counterfeit.
半端者なら洒落らんない成りじゃん
If you're half-baked, you can't laugh it off, can you?
お帰りの時間になって僕は思い通り
When it's time to go home, I get my way.
体感計で竦む また罵詈雑言インベイダー
Cowering on the sensory meter, the insult invader strikes again.
足が止まってる終芸 晒しにそうでも切りでするか
My feet are stopped at the final act; should I cut it even if it's exposed?
のらりくらり躱すわ
I'll dodge it lazily.
はじめまして神様
Nice to meet you, God.
もし救われるのなら 剥ぎ取るわ今から
If I'm to be saved, I'll strip it off right now.
Get down Get down 揺らめいて Get down Get down
Get down, get down, swaying... Get down, get down.
乗り込んだTwitter空間が 君を狂わしてんだ
The Twitter space you boarded is driving you mad.
雨降ったなら戻んの？ 泥ぬかるんで 行きと最後もアチュレイト
Will you go back if it rains? It's muddy, both the start and end are saturated.
どんな感度 そんなもんさ 虚しいわな
What kind of sensitivity? That's just how it is, how empty.
A-N-O-T-H-E-R
絡回ってく脳を乱してくれ
Derail my spinning brain
未来予想図なんか掻き消して
Erase any future plans
くだらない上手く描いたモノローグだって捨てて
Discarding even those worthless, well-written monologues
半端者ならばやれない マリアージュ
If you're half-hearted, you can't have this marriage
上書きの色になって 没は思い通り
Becoming an overwritten color, making failures go exactly as planned
ええじゃないか (作詞・作曲: マサ)
[Song: Isn't It Fine? (Lyrics/Music: Masa)]
パッパララー ここはきっと治らぬ狂い
Pappararaa, this is surely an incurable madness
声にもならん二声が
A second voice that cannot even make a sound
腹の底から競り上がるんだ
Swells up from the bottom of my stomach
冷めぬ空に押し殺す本能
Smothering my instinct in the uncooling sky
揺ら揺ら二色の海と
The swaying, two-colored sea and
揺れちゃって 温度が上昇中
Swaying along, the temperature is rising
空っぽな君は呟くんだ
The empty you mutters...
「人は永遠に...」
“People are forever...”
今 弾ける桃色
Now, a bursting peach color
ハイ ハイ ハイ 宙を舞って
Yes, yes, yes, dancing in the air
踊り狂うの
And dancing madly
ファッションビートで気取って
Pose with a fashion beat
ちんけな境地んじゃなーい
Not some cheap state of mind!
報われない悲しみ喰らってこう
Let's consume the unrewarded sadness
ファッションビートに染まって
Dyed in the fashion beat
言うことないなら息引き取っても
If you have nothing to say, even if you stop breathing
無駄だ ハイ ハイ ハイ
It's useless, yes, yes, yes
笑いましょうねえ
Let's laugh
ええじゃないか ええじゃないか
Isn't it fine? Isn't it fine?
この先は何にも分からんし
We don't know what lies ahead anyway
ブレじゃないか ブレじゃないか
Isn't it a blur? Isn't it a blur?
糞垂れ見てられんのー
You shitheads, I can't stand looking at you!
はっ 荒れ狂う世の中だから
Ah, because it's a wild world
ハイハイハイ 宙を舞って
Yes, yes, yes, dancing in the air
踊り狂うの
And dancing madly
ファッションビートで気取って
Pose with a fashion beat
ちんけな境地んじゃなーい
Not some cheap state of mind!
報われない悲しみ喰らってこう
Let's consume the unrewarded sadness
ファッションビートに染まって
Dyed in the fashion beat
言うことないなら息引き取っても
If you have nothing to say, even if you stop breathing
無駄だ ハイ ハイ ハイ
It's useless, yes, yes, yes
笑いましょうねえ
Let's laugh
あぁ 描いたようなストーリー
Ah, a story like the one I drew
僕の色
My color
濡れたほとりに落ち込んでいた
Falling into the wet shore
モノクロに尽きる日は
The day that runs out into monochrome
乗り越えられたら
If we can overcome it
あぁ今夜は笑って
Ah, laugh tonight
あの幽霊列車にキッスをして
And kiss that ghost train
七色に生まれ変わるのさ
To be reborn in seven colors
ファッションビートに染まって
Dyed in the fashion beat
言うことないなら息引き取っても
If you have nothing to say, even if you stop breathing
無駄だ ハイ ハイ ハイ
It's useless, yes, yes, yes
笑いましょうねえ
Let's laugh
はぁ、楽しっ！
Phew, that was so fun!
はぁ、やっぱり歌って踊るの楽しっ！イェーイ！イェーイ！
Phew, singing and dancing really is so much fun! Yay! Yay!
いや、ガチでちょっとぶちかましちゃったんですけど、どうも。
Seriously, I went a bit too wild out there. Hello.
え、なんか番長とかやってたんですか？
Wait, was Bancho or someone doing something?
え？お？なん、なんしか...え、なんか撮ってました？
Eh? Oh? What... wait, were you recording this?
え、なんか撮ってましたよね？え、てか、なんかこれ配信中？
Wait, you were recording me, right? Wait, is this streaming?
これ配信されてました？これ。ええ！？
Was this being streamed? This. What!?
ちょ、ちょ、著作権とかあるんですけど、一応。
Hey, wait, there's copyright and stuff, just so you know.
なん、コメントがすごい流れてるんですけど
Wow, the comments are scrolling so fast!
反転してて読めません
But they're mirrored, so I can't read them!
えっ、なんか、パチパチって、拍手してくれてて
Oh, you're clapping for me and typing 'clap clap'...
なんか、かっこよすぎるって、なぁに？
Wait, what's this about me being 'too cool'?
えっ、すごいなんか、えっ、え、草、草、なんか、草生やされた
Eh? Wow, you guys are spamming 'lol' at me!
え、なんか、なんか、ありがとうございました
U-Um, thank you so much!
ハッシュタグ、等々力はじめ生誕祭2026、って
And the hashtag, #TodorokiHajimeBirthdayFestival2026...
なんか、たくさんポストしてくれてるみたいなんですけど
It looks like you've been posting under it a lot!
なんだ、このタグ
What's with this tag anyway?
わかんないけど、はじめ祝ってもらってるし、ポストしてもらったら
I'm not sure, but since you're celebrating Hajime, if you post on it...
嬉しいかも、ありがとー
I'd be really happy! Thank you!
やっぱり、はじめ、歌ったり踊ったりするの好きで
Actually, Hajime really loves singing and dancing...
本当はこう、たくさんの人の前でパフォーマンスすることに憧れて
I've always dreamed of performing in front of a big crowd like this...
ちょっと、上京したいな、とか思ってるんですけど、ちょっと勇気が出なくて...
And I was thinking about moving to Tokyo, but I just didn't have the courage...
え？はじめなら大丈夫？いける？
Eh? "You'll be fine, Hajime"? "You can do it"?
え、コメントの方は、ちょっとどう思ってる？「可愛い」「なんて？」
U-Um, what do you guys in the comments think? "Cute"? "What"?
あれ、なんか思ってた...「ダンスうま！」すごい、褒められてる！
Wait, that's not what I expected... "Great dancing!" Wow, you're praising me!
「かっこいい！」あ、褒められてる！
"So cool!" Ah, you're praising me again!
よし！じゃあ、みんなにすごい勇気をもらったので、はじめ、行ってきます！
Alright! Since everyone gave me so much courage, Hajime is off!
夢を目指して、上京してくる！ありがとう！
I'm moving to Tokyo to chase my dreams! Thank you!
荒れ狂う季節の中を二人は一人きり
In the midst of these wild, stormy seasons, the two of us are all alone
さらり
Gliding through with ease
明け行く夕日の中を今夜も昼下がり
In the dawning sunset, tonight feels like early afternoon
さらり
Gliding through with ease
どれほど朽ち果てようと最後にゃ笑いたい
No matter how much we rot away, I want to laugh in the end
何のために戦おうとも動機は愛がいい
Whatever we fight for, I want the motive to be love
新しい日々は探さずとも常に
Even if we don't look for them, new days are always...
ここに
...right here
色々見てきたけれどこの瞳は永遠に
I've seen many different things, but these eyes of mine will forever...
きらり
...shine brightly
あれほど生きてきたけど全ては夢みたい
I've lived through so much, but it all feels like a dream
あれもこれも魅力的でも私は君がいい
This and that are both charming, but I prefer you
どこにいたの 探してたよ
Where were you? I was looking for you
連れてって 連れてって
Take me with you, take me with you
何もかも 捨ててくよ
I'll abandon everything and go
どこまでも どこまでも
No matter how far, no matter how far
荒れ狂う 季節の中も 群衆の中も
Through the stormy seasons, and through the crowds
君とならば さらり さらり
As long as I'm with you, we can glide through easily, easily
新しい日々も 拙い過去も 全てがきらり
New days and my clumsy past, they all shine brightly
無くしてしまったものを振り返って ほろり
Reflecting on the things I've lost, a tear sheds silently
時には途方に暮れてただ風に吹かれて ゆらり
At times, lost and bewildered, just swaying as the wind blows
行き先は決めたの
I've decided on my destination
迷わずに行きたいけど保証はしないよ
I want to go without hesitation, but I can't make any guarantees
何か分かったようで
Like I've figured something out...
だけどそれが分かって本当に良かった
But I'm really glad to know just that.
新しい日々は探さずとも常に ここに
Even if we don't look for new days, they are always here
常にここに ここに ここに
Always here, right here, right here
色々見てきたけれどこの瞳は
I've seen many things, but these eyes...
永遠にきらり
...will sparkle forever.
生きてきたけれど全ては夢みたい
I've lived that much, but it all seems like a dream
あれもこれも魅力的でも私は君がいい
Everything is attractive, but I want you
どこにいたの
Where were you?
探してたよ
I was searching for you
連れてって 連れてって
Take me away, take me away
何もかも 捨ててくよ保存
I'll throw everything away
どこまでも どこまでも保存
No matter how far, no matter how far
荒れ狂う 季節の中も
Even in the stormy seasons
群衆の中も
And even in the crowd
君とならば さらり さらり
If I'm with you, simply, simply
新しい日々も 拙い過去も
New days and clumsy pasts
全てがきらり
Everything is sparkling
Welcome to our Theater
ほら 踊れば
Look, if you dance
幕開けの合図が
The signal for the curtain call...
It's coming back
月火から水木金お疲れ Everybody clap your hands
Thanks for your hard work Mon to Fri, everybody clap your hands
待ちわびた金土日さあ Come on bring all your friends
The long-awaited Fri, Sat, and Sun, come on bring all your friends
世間は Work work 目線は Low low 心も体もボロボロです
The world goes 'work work,' eyes look low, low, mind and body are worn out
ガンバリアンな日本人に Everybody clap your hands
To the hard-working Japanese, everybody clap your hands
言えない Yes or No うんざりしちゃって
Tired of being unable to say yes or no
何もかも台無しな Routine 染み込んだ癖
Everything's ruined by routine, an ingrained habit
人のせい また自分のせい 憧れ持ったあの新天地へ
Blaming others, blaming myself, aiming for that promised land I longed for
結局はいつも通りさ
In the end, it's just business as usual
過ぎ去っていく Day by day
Passing by day by day
考えたって There's no best other way
Even if I think about it, there's no best other way
向かい風も味方にして Let's fly away
Turning even the headwind into an ally, let's fly away
Welcome to our Theater ほら 踊れば
Welcome to our Theater, look, if you dance
幕開けの合図が It's coming back
The signal for the curtain call, it's coming back
波瀾万丈な人生くらいがちょうどいいのさ
A life full of ups and downs is just about right
君が作る Showtime を見せて見せて頂戴
Show me the showtime that you create, please show me
春夏過ぎ秋冬に あれあれ Everybody clap your hands
Spring and summer pass, to autumn and winter, my, my, everybody clap your hands
ギリギリ駆け込んで間に合うかの Never-ending game
Rushing in at the last minute, wondering if we'll make it in this never-ending game
気持ちは Go go されどノロノロ 現実はそう甘くないね
Our spirits say 'go, go' but we move so slow, reality isn't that sweet
働き者な日本人に Everybody clap your hands
To the hard-working Japanese, everybody clap your hands
お決まりのルーティン 代わり映えない Myself
The usual routine, my uninspiring self
どれもこれも色のない世界に興味ない
I have no interest in a world completely devoid of color
ありのままの心が笑える場所へ Let's fly away
To a place where my true heart can smile, let's fly away
Welcome to our Theater ほら 踊れば
Welcome to our Theater, look, if you dance
幕開けの合図が It's coming back
The signal for the curtain call, it's coming back
波瀾万丈な人生くらいがちょうどいいのさ
A life full of ups and downs is just about right
君が作る Showtime を見せて見せて...
Show me the showtime that you create...
過ぎ去っていく Day by day
Passing by day by day
考えたって There's no best other way
Even if I think about it, there's no best other way
向かい風も味方にして Let's fly away
Turning even the headwind into an ally, let's fly away
Welcome to our Theater ほら 踊れば
Welcome to our Theater, look, if you dance
幕開けの合図が It's coming back
The signal for the curtain call, it's coming back
波瀾万丈な人生くらいがちょうどいいのさ
A life full of ups and downs is just about right
君が作る Showtime を見せて見せて頂戴
Show me the showtime that you create, please show me
とびきり Showtime 誰でも Showtime
The ultimate showtime, everyone's showtime
あなたの Showtime を見せて頂戴
Show me your showtime, please show me
とびきり Showtime 誰でも Showtime
The ultimate showtime, everyone's showtime
あなたの Showtime を見せて頂戴
Show me your showtime, please show me
はい！
Yes!
あ、みんな！星街すいせいちゃんのチャンネルですよ！
Ah, everyone! This is Hoshimachi Suisei-chan's channel!
ご存知かしら？ありがとう！
Do you know it? Thank you!
あ、みんな！なんか、超偶然に出会っちゃって...
Ah, everyone! It was like a total coincidence meeting up...
一緒に歌えて嬉しかったりする？
Are you happy we got to sing together?
私も嬉しかったわ
I was happy too.
うわー嬉しい！嬉しい、ちゃん！
Wow, I'm so glad! I'm so glad!
ありがとう
Thank you.
えっ、でも、でもあの...このシアター、勝手に入ってんですか？
Um, but, but... did we just enter this theater without permission?
まあ...駄目かもしれないわ
Well... we might not be allowed to.
駄目なの！？
We're not allowed?!
うん
Yeah.
えっ、じゃ怒られる？怒られる？
Wait, will we get yelled at? Will we?
まあ、怒られるわ
Well, we will definitely get yelled at.
なんでここ連れてきてくれたんですか！？
Why did you bring me here then?!
あそこの人がもう銃構えてるわ、こうやって
That person over there is already aiming a gun, like this.
怖い、怖い！そんな、ブッシュマンなの？何者？
Scary, scary! Are they some kind of bushman? Who is that?
あ、違う、あの、この人、オーディション...出場者よ、ね！
Ah, wait, no, this person... is an audition contestant!
こうやって、オーディションやってるんで、オーディション出場者でいこう、ね！
They're holding auditions like this, so let's pretend to be audition contestants, okay?
え、どういうこと！？
Wait, what do you mean?!
そういうことでいこう、ね！ここでオーディションやってるんだ！
Let's go with that! They're holding auditions here!
ここでオーディションやってるんだ
They're holding auditions here...
そうだよ！受けた方がいいんじゃない？じゃないと撃たれる！
That's right! You should probably audition. Otherwise we'll be shot!
怖い、怖いよー！
Scary! I'm scared!
あれ、星街すいせいじゃない！？
Wait, isn't that Hoshimachi Suisei?!
いっ、いけねえ！じゃーねー！
Oh crap! See ya!
えっ、すいちゃん、やばい、えっ！？
Wait, Sui-chan, this is bad, wait!
あれ、すいちゃん？ ええ、どっち？
Wait, Sui-chan? Uh, which way?
ステップはお静かに
[Song: Keep your steps quiet]
Step like, silent 踊るの Party, Party time
Step like, silent, dancing in the party, party time
抜き足 差し足 忍び足 甘い空中劇場
Slinking, sliding, sneaking footsteps, sweet aerial theater
Step by step, starry night 教えるわ
Step by step, starry night, I'll teach you
心の思うままに 躍らせて
Letting my heart dance as it pleases
強気な秘密 隠して
Hiding a confident secret
そっと口元笑って
With a soft smile on my lips
上品な蹴り上げ
An elegant high-kick
静かにちょっと豪快らしく
Quietly, with a touch of grand style
仕留めてあげるわ
I'll finish you off
Step like, same dance バックステップじゃ駄目
Step like, same dance, a backstep won't do
Feel like, もう一人の自分に勝つの
Feel like, winning against my other self
だって 盗まれたら 取り返すのが基本でしょ
After all, if it's stolen, it's basic to take it back, right?
タップ、合図をして 静かにあしらって
Tap, give the signal, and handle it quietly
ひらりとかわして逃げのびて
Lightly dodging and escaping
さらりと手には証拠ちゃん
Slyly, with the proof in hand
華麗に無音に逃げ切る
Splendidly, silently making a clean getaway
静かにちょっと豪快らしく
Quietly, with a touch of grand style
仕留めてあげるわ
I'll finish you off
Step like 奪い返し 踊るの Party, Party time
Step like, stealing it back, dancing in the party, party time
抜き足 差し足 忍び足 甘い空中劇場
Slinking, sliding, sneaking footsteps, sweet aerial theater
Step by step... その心のまま踊るわ
Step by step... I'll dance with my heart as it is
ずっとついてきてね
Follow me forever
踏み出してしてみてよ
Take a step forward
ここで決めるの
Decide it right here
誰も奪わせやしないわ
I'll won't let anyone steal it
胸に秘めた宝石を
The gem hidden in my heart
静かに踊って
Dance quietly
静かに踊ってよ
Dance quietly, please
ステップはお静かに
Keep your steps quiet
BAD HATTER
[Song: BAD HATTER]
Switching 何にでもなれるチェンジ くるくるタクト転がそう
Switching, a change to become anything, let's spin the baton round and round
Sweetie nightにMary Jane
Sweetie night in Mary Jane
かかとカンカンtapする伽藍堂
Heels tap-tap in the empty temple hall
secret sign ほらご招待
A secret sign, look, you're invited
洒落た帽子とステッキでnavigate
Navigate with a stylish hat and cane
step inside, gonna lunatic
すでに高揚していてグレイビーソース
Already getting hyped up, gravy sauce
さぁ乾杯してbillie jean
Come on, let's toast to Billie Jean
今はこの欲望に溺れよう
Now let's drown in this desire
有限なら夜が明ける前まで
If it's finite, then until the night breaks
味わいつくすべき
We should savor it to the end
you are "BAD HATTER"
親愛なるmonster
Dear monster
we are "BAD HATTER"
名声も罪状もナンセンス
Fame and charges are nonsense
bump! bump! moon night
渋滞のダンスフロア
Traffic jam on the dance floor
we are "stakeholder"
狂騒に飲まれ踊れ
Drown in the frenzy and dance
ブラッディサムとaviation
Bloody Sam and aviation
常に空中飛び交う金銀銅
Gold, silver, and bronze always flying in the air
会場内なら平等さ
Inside the venue, everyone is equal
老いも若きも化かし語り合う
Old and young alike, deceiving and talking to each other
step inside, gonna lunatic
誰も彼もが耳打ちcrazy talk
Everyone whispering crazy talk
一緒にどうですお嬢さん
How about joining me, miss?
角を生やした紳士がshall we dance?
Shall we dance with the horned gentleman?
幽霊とかどんな見た目だろうが
Whether they're a ghost or what they look like
気にする暇もない
I don't have time to worry about it
you are "BAD HATTER"
親愛なるmonster
Dear monster
we are "BAD HATTER"
名声も罪状もナンセンス
Fame and charges are nonsense
bump! bump! moon night
渋滞のダンスフロア
Traffic jam on the dance floor
we are "stakeholder"
狂騒に飲まれ踊れ
Drown in the frenzy and dance
ドゥビドゥバドゥビデッデッデデルダ デビデビドゥドゥデッデッデルドゥ
(Scat singing)
ドゥビダブルゲッゲドゥドラドゥッブダビディッダールッタディビデルッ
ダンダンダンダンダンダンデダンダンダンダンダンダンダンダンダッダドゥ
(Scat singing)
アッパディッドゥッタラドゥッタラディバジュバディダルダーディビッパビッペドゥー
you are "BAD HATTER"
親愛なるmonster
Dear monster
we are "BAD HATTER"
名声も罪状もナンセンス
Fame and charges are nonsense
bump! bump! moon night
渋滞のダンスフロア
Traffic jam on the dance floor
we are "stakeholder"
狂騒に飲まれ踊れ
Drown in the frenzy and dance
うわっ！お前、ちゃっかり居るじゃん！
Whoa! You're here, acting all casual!
何持ってるの？
What are you holding?
お、ば、バツ？！
O- Oh, an X?!
えっ、バツってどういうこと、おま...
Wait, what do you mean by an X? You...
も、もしかして、おわりちゃんの審査員だったの？！
Co- Could it be, you were Owari-chan's judge?!
え、だってさっき...
B- But just now...
なんかノリノリでドゥビドゥバドゥビデッデッデッてやってたじゃん！
You were totally getting into it, doing like 'Dubidubadubidettedette'!
えっ、出てけって？
Wait, 'get out'?
なんなんだよ！
What is your problem?!
おわり頑張った！ちょっと...ちょっと退いてって！
Owari tried her best! Wait... move over a bit!
ねえ！
Hey!
あれ？
Huh?
なん、なんか...体が...動かないんだけど。
Wh- Why... can't I... move my body?
よし、な、なんか離したくてもダメみたいだ。
Oof... I- It seems I can't let go of it even if I try.
なんだよ、こっちから！願い下げだ、こんな、こんな地獄！出てってやるー！
Fine! I didn't want to be here anyway, in this- this hell! I'm leaving!
はあ、はあ...
*Heavy breathing*
ちょっと待ってよ！ちょ、追いつけ、追いつけないよ！
Wait! I- I can't catch up!
何なんだよー！
What the heck is this?!
はあ、見失っちゃった...
Phew, I lost them...
はあ... うわぁ... うう... もう...
*Groaning* Jeez...
no thank you, alright?
能天気 どうかしている
Carefree, losing my mind
不適切 指摘には低姿勢で
"Inappropriate", "Be low-profile to criticism"
正義し放題 mr. x 放火している
Justice done freely, Mr. X is setting fires
真偽不明なんて
With "truth unknown"
正気じゃない
that's not sane
夜は on and on and on
Night is on and on and on
僕ら怨念飲んでへべれけじゃん
We're drinking up our grudges and getting smashed
目には？歯には？ 簡単だ
For the eyes? For the teeth? It's simple
吸って吐いてジャッジメント
Inhale and exhale, judgment
ようやく今晩無礼講決行です
Finally, tonight, everything goes
皆様ナンセンス 甚だナンセンス
Everyone is nonsense, very nonsense
イキる勿れ黙れ黙れ
Don't be cocky, shut up, shut up
この世はナンセンス 誠に遺憾です<
This world is nonsense, I'm truly sorry
お気の毒ね 哀れ哀れ仕方ねぇ
Too bad, you poor thing, poor thing, it can't be helped
ほら精々気張っていってらっしゃい
Come on, try your best and go
じゃ閻魔によろしく言っといて
Then, give my regards to Enma
be quiet, alright?
拡声器セールしている
Selling megaphones
名義不明だとしてもまいどあり
"Even if the owner is unknown, thank you for your business"
夜にカーテンコールを
Curtain call in the night
まさに宣言通り dirty party night
Just as declared, dirty party night
右も左も断頭台
Right and left, guillotine
降って湧いたチェックメイト
sudden checkmate
ようやく今晩無礼講決行です
Finally, tonight, everything goes
皆様ナンセンス 甚だナンセンス
Everyone is nonsense, very nonsense
イキる勿れ黙れ黙れ
Don't be cocky, shut up, shut up
この世はナンセンス 誠に遺憾です
This world is nonsense, I'm truly sorry
お気の毒ね 哀れ哀れ
Too bad, you poor thing, poor thing...
can’t you understand?
can't you understand?
yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah
yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah
街並みに宣言通り Darling, darling night
As declared on the city streets, darling, darling night
右も左もDon't cry ふてぶてしくチェックメイト
Right and left, don't cry, audaciously checkmate
ようやく今晩ブレイク結果提示
Finally tonight, breaking and presenting the results
目覚ましナンセンス はなはだナンセンス
An eye-opening nonsense, utterly nonsense
切る流る 黙れ 黙れ 黙れ
Cutting and flowing, shut up, shut up, shut up
この世はナンセンス 誠に遺憾です
This world is nonsense, it is truly regrettable
お気の毒ね
How pitiful for you
暴れ 暴れ 暴れ
Rampage, rampage, rampage
Can't you understand?
Yeah yeah yeah yeah
目覚ましナンセンス はなはだナンセンス
An eye-opening nonsense, utterly nonsense
切る流る 黙れ 黙れ 黙れ
Cutting and flowing, shut up, shut up, shut up
この世はナンセンス はなからナンセンス
This world is nonsense, nonsense from the start
切る流る 黙れ 黙れ 黙れ
Cutting and flowing, shut up, shut up, shut up
まもなく時間です 誠に遺憾です
Time will soon be up, it is truly regrettable
お気は済んだ？ 下がれ 下がれ くたばれ
Are you satisfied yet? Back off, back off, drop dead
ほら成績表だって言ってんでしょう
Look, I told you it's a report card
体調崩しちゃっていいから
It's fine even if you ruin your health
So rest in peace
ってごめん嘘
Just kidding, sorry
来世で会おう See you again!
Let's meet in the next life, see you again!
うわー！
Whoa!
そこの位置、あぶにゃ！ 危ないんじゃないですか？
Oh, that spot is dangerous-nyan! Isn't that dangerous?
え？
Huh?
何ちゅーその動き、お前... ダンサー？
What kind of movement is that? Are you... a dancer?
え、ダンサーですけど。
Uh, yes, I'm a dancer.
私も！ダンサーです！
Me too! I'm a dancer!
えっ！？なんかすごいダンサーがいっぱい出てきた！
Huh!? A bunch of amazing dancers just appeared!
え、なんか、はじめ、さっきダンサーのオーディション落ちちゃってさ...
Well, actually, I, Hajime, just failed a dancer audition...
もしかして、あそこのシアターですか？
Could it be the theater over there?
え、そう！
Yes, that's the one!
えっ、それ私も落ちました！
Huh, I failed that one too!
えーー！
Eeeh!
僕も！
Me too!
え、わたし、わたしも！
Wait, me too!
ええーー！みんな落ちた仲間！？
Eeeh! Are we all fellow failures!?
うわーー！
Yeah!
ねえ...
Hey...
あのミニ番長審査員センスないよな！
That mini-bancho judge has zero taste, right!
ほんとに！センスない！
Exactly! Zero taste!
いやいや、うちらのダンス、ちゃんと見せつけてやろうじゃん！
No, let's show them what our dancing is really made of!
おーー！
Yeah!
もう壁とは踊らないぞ！ 儒烏風亭らでん！
I won't dance with walls anymore! Juufuutei Raden!
3メートルの覇気、こぼ・かなえる！
3-meter conqueror's Haki, Kobo Kanaeru!
カオスに落ちる、ハコス・ベールズ！
Falling into chaos, Hakos Baelz!
宇宙一の番長になる、轟はじめ！
Becoming the universe's number one bancho, Todoroki Hajime!
よし！うちらの始まりは...
Alright! Our beginning starts...
こっから！
From here!
Check out the bridge!
俺 悪くない
I'm not in the wrong,
何も間違ってない
I've done nothing incorrect.
自分じゃない
It wasn't me,
何かのせいにしたい
I want to blame it on something else.
天才じゃないの？
Aren't you a genius?
だったら交わしなさい
Then get out of the way.
これフィクションじゃない
This isn't fiction,
よく見なさい
take a close look.
天分の才などない
I have no natural talent,
でも
but still...
やめられない
I can't stop,
見たい
I want to see.
あたしゃアホウかバカみたい
Am I a fool? I look like an idiot.
天才？こっから！
Genius? Starting now!
ロールモデル？メラメラ！
Role model? Burning up!
まだまだ自分で決めつけんな
Not yet! Don't define it yourself.
限界？突破！
Limit? Break it!
さらけ出せお前らの正解
Show us your true answer.
本当の自分なんて居やしねえよ
There's no such thing as your "real self."
輝くなきゃ駄目！
If you don't shine, no!
勝ち続けなきゃ駄目！
If you don't keep winning, no!
って思い込んでることこそが駄目！
Thinking like that is exactly what's wrong!
好きこそ物の上手なれ
What you like, you will do well.
継ぎ接ぎこそ終える根競べ
A contest of endurance to finish the patchwork.
I can't be someone else, oh I know, I know...
このブレーキを壊したいの したいの
I want to break this brake, I want to...
足の甲から 脳天に響け
Echo from the instep to the crown of your head!
道なき道ほど 進め
Go forward the pathless path!
魂 魂になるねんや
My soul is becoming real soul!
Let it fire!
燃やすこの闘志 その鉄格子
Burn this fighting spirit, break this iron bar,
ぶち壊し どうしようもないままが自分なんだ
breaking it down! Leaving it hopeless, that is myself,
こっから始まんだ
it starts from here!
いつかの童心もって努力し
With the childhood heart of some day, I'll put in the effort,
夢と相思相愛になれるはずなんだ
I should be able to become mutually in love with my dreams.
こっから、こっから始まんだ
It starts from here, it starts from here...
1, 2, 3, 4 順番通り 行ってないだけで予定通り
1, 2, 3, 4, just not going in order, it's still according to plan.
ローリンローリン 転がってけ
Rollin' rollin', keep rolling,
よりどりみどりの一生
a life with many choices.
1, 2, 3, 4 順番通り 行ってないだけで予定通り
1, 2, 3, 4, just not going in order, it's still according to plan.
ローリンローリン 転がってけ yo
Rollin' rollin', keep rolling, yo,
こっから始まんだ
it starts from here.
数年後...
A few years later...
Haa, haa, haa, haa...
I can't see what's behind those eyes
Just wait だから let it all out before the night
Just wait, so let it all out before the night.
誰かの理想像に 耳を傾けてしまっているの？
Are you listening to someone else's ideal image of you?
I can't take it no more
I guess it's time to let it go now
感情のない世界に溺れてさ
Drowning in a world with no emotions,
Tell me who I'm supposed to be
I'm lost with all your honesty
I'll stop playing, say no more
Don't let me down
Down, down, down...
Do you see what you came for? 狂ったように mind, mind
Do you see what you came for? Like crazy, mind, mind!
Say you wanna be a superstar, yeah show me what you got
You're not gonna break, fall apart
Haa, haa, haa, haa...
Let me higher, higher!
Show me what you got, you're not gonna break, fall apart
何かを言おうとして
Trying to say something,
間違い探しのスタート合図
it's the cue to start spot-the-difference.
Why's everybody's eyes on me?
慣れてしまうものね 視線の矛先
I guess I've gotten used to where the gazes point.
I can't take it no more
I guess it's time to let it go now
感じるプレッシャー 押し殺してさ
Crushing down the pressure I feel...
Tell me who I'm supposed to be
I'm lost with all your honesty
I'll stop playing, say no more
Don't let me down
Down, down, down...
Do you see what you came for? 狂ったように mind, mind
Do you see what you came for? Like crazy, mind, mind!
Say you wanna be a superstar, yeah show me what you got
You're not gonna break, fall apart
Haa, haa, haa, haa...
Let me higher, higher!
Show me what you got, you're not gonna break, fall apart
Yeah, say you wanna be a superstar
So show me what you got
I can't take it no more
I guess it's time to let it go now
感情のない世界に溺れてさ
Drowning in a world with no emotions,
Tell me who I'm supposed to be
I'm lost with all your honesty
I'll stop playing, say no more
Don't let me down
Down, down, down...
Do you see what you came for? 狂ったように mind, mind
Do you see what you came for? Like crazy, mind, mind!
Say you wanna be a superstar, yeah show me what you got
You're not gonna break, fall apart
Haa, haa...
higher, higher
Show me human fucking...
わぁ！みんなー！ありがとう！
Wow! Everyone! Thank you!
えー、仲間と励まし合って、みんなから勇気をもらって、
Um, encouraging each other with my friends, getting courage from everyone,
こうして、ステージに立って、たくさんの人の前で、パフォーマンスすることができました！ありがとうございました！
standing on stage like this, I was able to perform in front of so many people! Thank you very much!
そして！なんと！Xトレンド1位！ありがとうございます！
And! Unbelievably! No. 1 on X trending! Thank you very much!
そして、チャンネル登録者様も、120万人様にいったみたいで、本当にありがとうございます！
And, it looks like my channel subscribers reached 1.2 million, thank you so much!
うわぁ！嬉しい！
Wow! I'm so happy!
こうしてね、こう夢を追いかけて、上京して、
Chasing my dream and moving to Tokyo like this,
こう、たくさんの人のスターになることができました！轟はじめ、うわぁ！
I was able to become a star to so many people! Todoroki Hajime, wow!
でもね、この、物語を作るにあたって、
But, you know, in creating this story,
たくさんの素敵なアーティストちゃんの楽曲をお借りして、あの、することができましたので、本当にありがとうございます！
I was able to borrow songs from many wonderful artists, so thank you so much!
はじめも、曲をたくさん作れるように頑張ります！
I'll also do my best to make lots of songs!
そして、これがはじめの100万人記念の新衣装になりまーす！
And, this is Hajime's new outfit celebrating 1 million subscribers!
衣装の名前は、ボーダーコードだ衣装でーす！
The outfit's name is the Border Code outfit!
市原達也さんに仕立てていただきました！
It was tailored by Tatsuya Ichihara!
あ、ね！みなさんが応援してくれたおかげです！ありがとうございます！
Ah, right? It's all thanks to everyone supporting me! Thank you very much!
で、今回の新衣装ね、髪が、お団子！
And about this new outfit, my hair is in buns!
そして、足がなんか、凄く長く見えるデザインで、
Also, the design makes my legs look really long...
ほら！太ももも見えちゃう！ね！
Look! You can even see my thighs! Right?
みなさん、なんかおかしくない？
Everyone, isn't something strange?
ぴょこぴょこがない！
There are no hair wiggles!
嘘だ！そんな馬鹿な！そんな馬鹿な！
No way! That's impossible! That's impossible!
ぴょこぴょこがないだとう？！
No hair wiggles?!
うわぁ、嘘でーす！ぴょこぴょこもありまーす！
Whoa, just kidding! The hair wiggles are here too!
ま、ぴょこぴょこないと、脳みそ出ちゃうからね。必要だよね！
Well, without the hair wiggles, my brains would spill out. So they're necessary!
であと、ジャケットも脱げます！ほら！ほら、タクティカル！うりゃ！
Also, I can take the jacket off! Look! Look, tactical! Yah!
こうして、この後のメン限で紹介するので、気になる方は見に来てください！
I will showcase this in the members-only stream after this, so if you're curious, please come watch!
え、続いて、なんと、新曲を披露しようと思いまーす！
And next, I'm going to perform my new song!
みなさん、盛り上がる準備、できてますかー？！うぉーーい！
Is everyone ready to get hyped?! Woah!
お団子可愛い？ありがとう！
Are the buns cute? Thank you!
とてもね、格好良くて、なんか、セクシーな感じの曲になってるので、ぜひ、聴いてください！
It's a really cool and somewhat sexy song, so please listen to it!
それでは、いきます！Deep Dive！
Here we go! Deep Dive!
late night 今夜は with my girlies
late night tonight with my girlies
baby すぐ出なよ (let's get party, yeah)
baby, come out right now (let's get party, yeah)
頭からつま先 キメてる lips
From head to toe, looking sharp with my lips
okay, ma ladies I need you to show me
wow マジ gorgeous, thanks
wow, really gorgeous, thanks
you look so badass
scream, scream, scream and shout ay
(scream, scream, scream and shout)
wow マジ gorgeous, thanks
wow, really gorgeous, thanks
you look so badass
scream, scream, scream and shout ay
turn it up now let go
me and my girls, me and my girls
見てよ we're amazing, we are so amazing
Look, we're amazing, we are so amazing
me and my girls, me and my girls ここから dive
me and my girls, me and my girls, dive from here
yes, i'm a hot queen
dive, let's deep dive, i wanna deep dive
dive, yeah deep dive, ay, ay, ay
dive, yeah deep dive, yeah, yeah, yeah
let's get out of control
girl
you like it like that
まじ you're so hot
seriously, you're so hot
burn
まさに queen
truly a queen
hot queen hot queen
ワンストロークで star, glow
star, glow in one stroke
bare minimum でも hard core
bare minimum, but hard core
ネイル光って so shiny
nails shining so bright, so shiny
マスカラして i'm burning
mascara on, i'm burning
髪down? それともpony?
Hair down? Or maybe a pony?
ooh-la-la ooh-la-la
視線をcontrol
Control the gaze
i don't mind them
誰かのapproval
somebody's approval
i don't need it at all
wow マジ gorgeous, thanks
wow, really gorgeous, thanks
you look so badass
scream...
Gimme gimme show time! Hey! Turn it up now, make up!
Gimme gimme showtime! Hey! Turn it up now, make up!
Are you ready? Are you ready, ready to go?
Me and my girls, me and my girls, we gotta, we gotta, we gotta, we gotta, we gotta, we gotta win
Crazy crazy
Let's get back to beat. You're my heart queen!
Dive, let's deep dive. I wanna deep dive.
Dive, your deep dive. Hey, hey, hey!
Dive, your deep dive. Let's get it on, let's get it on.
Girl, you look like that, girl. 街を騒がす bad
Girl, you look like that, girl. Stirring up the town, bad
まさに queen, hot queen, hot queen!
Just like a queen, hot queen, hot queen!
Girl, you look like that, girl. 街を騒がす bad
Girl, you look like that, girl. Stirring up the town, bad
まさに queen, hot queen, hot queen!
Just like a queen, hot queen, hot queen!
はい、ということで、生誕グッズが出ました！
Yes! And so, my birthday merchandise is out!
轟はじめ誕生日記念2026のフルセットはこんな感じです！
This is the Todoroki Hajime Birthday Celebration 2026 Full Set!
一つずつ紹介していきまーす！
Let me introduce them one by one!
一つ目！ぶんぶんぱんちょーアクリルスタンド！
First! The Bunbun Bancho Acrylic Stand!
イラストは、A5き先生に描いていただきました！
The illustration was drawn by A5ki-sensei!
台座がね、フチがあるので、座ってる風にも、いろんなフチに、机とかのフチに引っかけても使えます！
Since the base has an edge, you can display it as if she's sitting on a desk edge or any edge!
怒っているのがポイントです！
Her angry expression is the highlight!
二つ目は、はじめとおそろいチョーカー！
Second is the matching choker with Hajime!
はじめの新衣装とおそろいのチョーカーです！星のチャームが可愛い！
It's a choker matching Hajime's new outfit! The star charm is so cute!
首のサイズが合わないよっていう方は、痛バッグなどに、つけてください！
For those whose neck size doesn't fit, please attach it to your ita-bag!
三つ目は、BANCHOジャージ！
Third is the BANCHO Track Jacket!
えー、裏面のイラストは、おもちチャウダーちゃんに描いていただきました！
The illustration on the back was drawn by Omochi Chowder-chan!
表面は刺繍になってます。
The front has embroidery.
スバル先輩のね、生地がとても良かったので、同じのにしていただきました！
Since Subaru-senpai's jacket material was so good, I had them make it with the same material!
最後、ぬいぐるみキーホルダー、ブラックオーロラ衣装バージョン！
Finally, the Plushie Key Chain, Black Aurora Outfit Version!
初めて出した人気のぬいぐるみの、新衣装バージョンです！
It's the new outfit version of the popular plushie we released for the first time!
あの時買えなかったよっていう方、ぜひお迎えしてください！
Those who couldn't buy it back then, please do welcome her home!
そして、フルセット特典はこちら！
And here is the full set bonus!
今回のライブの、チケット風カード！全員に直筆サイン書かせていただきます！
A ticket-style card from today's live concert! I will personally hand-sign each one!
えー、去年のね、ライブでたくさんグッズを買っていただいたおかげで、
Thanks to everyone buying so much merchandise at last year's concert,
今年もこんなに、力を入れることができました！ありがとうございます！
we were able to put so much effort into it again this year! Thank you so much!
今回のライブも楽しんでいただけただろうか？
I hope you enjoyed today's live concert too!
ぜひね、グッズもお迎えしていただけると、今後の励みになります！よろしくお願いします！
If you could also get the merchandise, it will motivate me going forward! Thank you!
以上、グッズ紹介でしたー！
That's all for the merchandise introduction!
あー、しんどかった！
Ah, that was exhausting!
このあと、ラストスパート！
Next up is the last spurt!
一緒に盛り上がっていってください、いきますよー！えい！
Let's keep getting hyped up together! Here we go! Yeah!
イェーイ！おー！
Yeah! Oh!
みんな、ありがとう！
Thank you, everyone!
はぁ！
Hah!
みんな、ありがとうございます！それでは、今回のライブに携わってくださった方をご紹介していきたいと思います！
Thank you so much, everyone! Now, I'd like to introduce the people who helped make this live show possible!
まずは、ダンサー！夢にゃー！
First, the dancers! Yumeya!
れちおにゃー！
Rechionya!
う、みなみゃー！
Mi... Minamya!
そらー！
Sora!
ありがとう！そして！この場にはいないんですけど、振付師のMiUキニシウラ先生！
Thank you! And, although they aren't here today, our choreographer MiU Kinishiura-sensei!
タップの、あか先生！
Aka-sensei for tap dance!
えー、ポッピン、ドド先生！
And Poppin' Dodo-sensei!
ダンス監修、ユカ先生！
Dance supervisor, Yuka-sensei!
ボーカル監修、マリア先生！
Vocal supervisor, Maria-sensei!
そして、ゲストにお越しいただきました、星街すいせいちゃん！
And our guests, Hoshimachi Suisei-chan!
ハコス・ベールズちゃん！
Hakos Baelz-chan!
伊崎莉緒奈ちゃん！
Izaki Riona-chan!
虹宮すうちゃん！本当にありがとうございました！
Nijimiya Suu-chan! Thank you so much!
そして、今見えない中で活動してくださっているスタッフの皆さん！
And to all the staff working behind the scenes where we can't see!
そして、星川の目の前にいてくれている、見てくれた皆々様！本当にありがとうございました！
And to everyone who is right here in front of me, and everyone who watched! Thank you so much!
それでは、ちょっと新曲について詳しくご紹介したいなと思います！
Now, I'd like to introduce my new song in more detail!
改めてタイトルは、Deep Dive！
Once again, the title is 'Deep Dive'!
はい！MV公開はこの配信のすぐ後です！
Yes! The MV will be released right after this stream!
音源リリースは本日24時からになります！皆さんたくさん聴いていただけると嬉しいです！
The digital release will be today at 24:00! I'd be really happy if you listened to it a lot!
さぁ、それではここで、重大発表いきたいと思います！こちらの動画をご覧ください！
Alright, now, I'd like to make a major announcement! Please watch this video!
星川サラ x FILA コラボ決定!!
[On-Screen: Hoshikawa Sara x FILA Collab Decided!!]
COMING SOON!!
[On-Screen: COMING SOON!!]
うわー！すごい！この度、星川とFILAさんのコラボが決定しました！
Wow! Amazing! This time, Hoshikawa and FILA are doing a collaboration!
うわー、嬉しい！ありがとうございます！
Wow, I'm so happy! Thank you so much!
そして、なんと！スニーカーを含むアパレルをプロデュースさせていただきました！
And, of course! I got to produce apparel including sneakers!
やったー！星川っぽいカラーリングを取り入れながら、男性でも女性でも似合うように意識してデザインしてみました！
Hooray! While incorporating Hoshikawa-like coloring, I designed it so that both men and women can wear it!
一足目、星川のこだわりを詰め込んだスニーカーにしていくので、続報を楽しみにしていてください！
For the first pair, we are making sneakers packed with Hoshikawa's attention to detail, so please look forward to more news!
えー、そして今回、なんとスニーカーだけじゃなくてね、ジャージとTシャツとキャップもプロデュースしちゃいました！
And this time, not only sneakers, but we also produced jerseys, T-shirts, and caps!
えー、さらに！コラボに当たって、オリジナルのコラボロゴをFILAさんと作りました！ドドン！
And even more! For this collaboration, we created an original collab logo with FILA! Ta-da!
うわー、可愛い！
Wow, so cute!
実は、このね、ロゴ、FILAさんと一緒に打ち合わせをして、あの、考えました、星川。
Actually, Hoshikawa came up with this logo through meetings with FILA.
あ、ここ、こういう感じね。実際にこう手書きをしながら、打ち合わせをして...
Ah, right here, like this. We had meetings while actually sketching...
どの色がいいかなって、いろんな色味を出してもらって、これにしました！
choosing which color would be best, seeing various color options, and we went with this!
一目でね、もう星川だってわかる、こう、ミニ番長のシルエットがいいかなと思って、入れてみました！
I thought a silhouette of Mini Bancho, which makes you recognize Hoshikawa at a glance, would be perfect, so I put it in!
えー、このロゴがね、コラボの商品にも付きます！
This logo will also be on the collaboration items!
実はね、アパレル以外にも、FILAさんとのコラボ商品が出ますので、皆さん詳細な情報が出るの、ぜひお楽しみに、お待ちください！
Actually, besides apparel, other collaboration items with FILA will also be released, so please wait excitedly for more detailed information!
えー、この後ですね、メンバー限定アンコールライブ、21時15分からありますし...
And after this, we have a member-only encore live starting at 21:15...
えー、この新曲についても色々詳しく見ていければと思いますので...
We'll also be looking at this new song in more detail, so...
ぜひまだの方は、チャンネル登録と、通知をオンにして、メンバーも入っていただけると、アンコールも一緒に楽しめて、ハッピーだなと思います！
if you haven't yet, please subscribe to the channel, turn on notifications, and join the membership so we can enjoy the encore together!
えー、おさらいをすると、新曲MV、この後すぐ公開！
To recap, the new song MV will be released right after this!
えー、21時からグッズ販売！21時15分からアンコールライブ！24時新曲音源リリースです！ありがとうね！
Goods on sale from 21:00! Encore live from 21:15! New song release at 24:00! Thank you!
それでは、メンバー限定アンコールライブでお会いしましょう！
Well then, see you at the member-only encore live!
バイバーイ！いっぱいコメントありがとう！嬉しかった！
Bye-bye! Thank you so much for all the comments! I was so happy!
はぁ、ありがと〜！
Phew... thank you~!
なおす組!!!
To the Naosu-gumi!!!
いつもぱめと楽しいを共有してくれてありがとう！
Thank you for always sharing fun times with Pame!
あなたが期待してくれるから もっとがんばりたい！もっと成長したいって思えるよ！
Because you expect great things from me, it makes me want to work harder and grow even more!
ぱめの歩みを支えてくれてありがとう♡
Thank you for supporting Pame's journey ♡
これからも一緒に、心地いい音を奏でていこうね！
Let's keep creating pleasant sounds together in the future!